When we are invited to eat, we love to
bring something.  But be careful,
it has to be well thought out and it absolutely mustn't
cost us too much.
So to be organized, I make a
list to avoid any slip-ups during
shopping, I bring my sweetheart along.  I
tend to wander around a bit,
buying things I don't
need.  He even thought about taking the
list for school supplies.  We dropped it off
at Bureau Vallée and asked them to
prepare it for us.  I went to Leclerc where I
bought everything I needed and then we went home
.  And thankfully so,
because there were really a lot of
people and I hate that.  And now we're
off.  All I have to do now is get
cooking.  I start with panotas
because they are quick to make and the
resting time is long.  So I put in my
liquid cream, vanilla powder,
sugar and I heat it all up.  I
add the gelatin and it's ready.
All I have to do is put them in my little jars and
they already look so good like
this.  I [music] put them in the fridge to
move on to the next step.  And if you're still
here, order food and tell me what
you would do if you were invited.  All I have to do is
chop my onions,
tomatoes and basil.  And in a pan
with butter, I'm going to put the
onions.  Add a little wine with
honey and let it caramelize like that.
I'm taking care of the tomatoes.  I mix it with
basil, olive oil and
pepper.  In a pie dish, I add
more olive oil to the bottom, honey
and vinegar cream.  I arrange
my beautiful tomatoes, add the
caramelized onions.  I put my shortcrust pastry
on top.  She's too beautiful.  I
put it in the oven and off we go.  My panotas
are practically ready.  Add
raspberry coulis with real
raspberries.  They look too good.
All I have to do is check my pie and it's
perfect.  And with a touch of
stratella, it's even better.  In short,
kisses.  Ms.